Contact

prv.maxim@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/maxschaefer-dev (LinkedIn)

www.maxschaefer.tech (pers.)

Top Skills

Deep Learning

Computer Vision

Machine Learning

PyTorch & TensorFlow

Languages

English (Full Professional)

German (Native or Bilingual)

Russian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

DeepLearning.Al TensorFlow Developer Specialization

Deep Learning Specialization

Deep Learning Engineer

TensorFlow: Advanced Techniques

Specialization

TensorFlow: Data and Deployment

Specialization

Honors-Awards

Top 2% (rank 19/854) - On Cloud N - Cloud Cover Detection Challenge

Top 3% (rank 23/713) – Mars Spectrometry: Detect Evidence for Past Habitability by NASA

Top 7% (rank 20/296) – Deep Chimpact: Depth Estimation for Wildlife Conservation

Top 8% (rank 33/403) - Data-Centric AI Competition

Max Schaefer

Co-Founder of Creation Brothers UG | Machine Learning/Deep Learning Engineer | Special interest in Computer Vision

Summary

Machine learning/deep learning engineer with special interest in computer vision. Actively participating in ML/DL competitions. Some of my latest results:

Top 2% (19/854) - On Cloud N - Cloud Cover Detection Challenge von Microsoft AI for Earth

Top 3% (23/713) – Mars Spectrometry: Detect Evidence for Past Habitability by NASA

Top 7% (20/296) – Deep Chimpact: Depth Estimation for Wildlife Conservation

Former IT Administrator with insights into the whole infrastructure of a medium-sized enterprise. I'm aware of the workflow a project needs and how to server it reliable. Furthermore, I experienced how difficult it gets to manage the IT infrastructure of over 600 employees. I listed my responsibilities in this field down below.

Experience

Creation Brothers UG

Co-Founder

April 2019 - Present (3 years 1 month)

Hamm, North Rhine-Westphalia, Germany

I built a print-on-demand online Shop und several affiliate-marketing sites. Had to wear a lot of hats. Responsibilities listed below:

- IT infrastructure (E-Mail, websites, hosting, DB, etc.)
- Product Manager & product Design
- Web Design, UI/UX, SEO (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Shopify Backend)
- Media & Logo Design (Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro)
- Marketing (Influencer Marketing)
- Social media presence
- Customer support

EWH Holding GmbH & Co.KG 6 years 8 months

IT-Systemadministrator

August 2015 - March 2019 (3 years 8 months)

Wickede, North Rhine-Westphalia, Germany

Responsibilities:

- SCCM configuration und automatic deployment
- Microsoft product licensing (MLP certificate)
- Windows Server & Workstations Deployment
- Administration of: Backup, Antivirus, E-Mail security, camera & digital locking system
- Purchasing, storing and deployment of hardware
- Active directory administration (user & user rights, system, inheritance etc.)

IT specialist (system integration)

August 2012 – July 2015 (3 years)

Wickede, North Rhine-Westphalia, Germany

Education

Hellweg Berufskolleg Unna Apprenticeship, IT specialist (System integration) – (Aug. 2012 – July 2015)

Peter-Weiss-Gesamtschule Unna Abitur – (Aug. 2008 – June 2012)